{"questions":[{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":false,"options":["JavaScript is is complementary to and integrated with HTML.","JavaScript is open and cross-platform.","Both of the above."],"answers":["Both of the above."],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"Both of the above options are correct."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"How can you get the total number of arguments passed to a function?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["Using args.length property","Using arguments.length property","Both of the above."],"answers":["Using arguments.length property"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"Using arguments.length property, we can get the total number of arguments passed to a function."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following is correct about callbacks?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["A callback is a plain JavaScript function passed to some method as an argument or option.","Some callbacks are just events, called to give the user a chance to react when a certain state is triggered.","Both of the above."],"answers":["Both of the above."],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"A callback is a plain JavaScript function passed to some method as an argument or option. Some callbacks are just events, called to give the user a chance to react when a certain state is triggered."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which built-in method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["substr()","getSubstring()","slice()","None of the above."],"answers":["substr()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"substr() method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following function of String object returns the character at the specified index?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["charAt()","charCodeAt()","concat()","indexOf()"],"answers":["charAt()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"charAt() ? Returns the character at the specified index."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["slice()","split()","substr()","substring()"],"answers":["substring()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"substring() ? Returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following function of String object creates a string to be displayed as bold as if it were in a <b> tag?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["anchor()","big()","blink()","bold()"],"answers":["bold()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"bold() ? Creates a string to be displayed as bold as if it were in a <b> tag."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["link()","sub()","sup()","small()"],"answers":["link()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"link() ? Creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following function of Array object creates a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in this array?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["push()","join()","pop()","map()"],"answers":["map()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"map() ? Creates a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in this array."},{"id":null,"category":null,"level":null,"question":"Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?","program":null,"type":"radio","showNumAnswers":null,"options":["toSource()","splice()","toString()","unshift()"],"answers":["toSource()"],"selected":null,"answerDescription":"toSource() ? Represents the source code of an object."}],"ref":"https://www.tutorialspoint.com/javascript/javascript_online_quiz.htm"}
